A Guide to the State Treasurer's Correspondence of the Virginia Dept. of the Treasury, 1962-2022
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
State Treasurer's Correspondence of the Virginia Dept. of the Treasury, 1962-2002
The Library of Virginia
38086, 54159
56 cubic feet (56 Boxes)
Virginia Dept. of the Treasury
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 38086 transferred from the Virginia Dept. of the Treasury on May 8, 2001.
Accession 54159 transferred from the Virginia Dept. of the Treasury on April 16, 2024.
Historical Information
OFrom 1691 to 1776, the Treasurer's Office was a powerful, independent agency. Following the adoption of the state constitution in May 1776, the treasurer has served as a fiscal agent subsidiary to the auditor of public accounts, then to the second auditor, as well, and finally, since March 1, 1928, to their successor, the comptroller. The treasurer kept separate books and sat on the board of directors for three significant funds: the Literary Fund (1811), the Internal Improvement Fund (1816), and the Sinking Fund (1835).
The office of treasurer was created to collect all the revenues raised from duties on skins, furs, and foreign liquors to support the College of William and Mary. From 1691 until 1723, the speaker of the House of Burgesses was appointed treasurer. The offices of speaker and treasurer were separated in 1766. In October 1776 the General Assembly established the auditor as the primary fiscal agent and in October 1778 specified the treasurer's subservient status to the auditor. The treasurer received and disbursed state money on warrants from the first or second auditor after the latter office was created in 1823 and kept accounts in books which he compared yearly with those of the two auditors. His basic duties remained unchanged from 1792 until March 1, 1928, when the Byrd plan for reorganizing state government went into effect.
On April 18, 1927 the Reorganization Act of 1927 created the Dept. of Finance, which included the Division of the Treasury, was created. The Office of Comptroller was created to perform the functions formerly exercised by the first and second auditors. The treasurer's basic duties still remained unchanged, but he now answered to the comptroller. A significant change required the comptroller to audit each claim to determine its validity before he authorized the treasurer to make payment. In addition, these two officers were designated Commissioners of the Sinking Fund and, along with the governor, members of the Finance Board. A 1928 amendment to the Reorganization Act of 1927 required the treasurer to make daily reports of all receipts to the comptroller, and to take custody of all bonds and certificates of the state debt.
The Treasurer is now a gubernatorial appointment. A 1948 Act of the General Assembly changed the Division of Treasury to the Department of Treasury. The 1950 revision of the Code of Virginia stipulated that a treasury board was to replace both the Finance Board and the Commissioners of the Sinking Fund. The treasurer, comptroller, and state tax commissioner were designated as members of this board. They were responsible for supervising all investments of state funds, for designating state depositories, for managing the Sinking Fund, and for any other matters which might be conferred upon them by law.
In 1972 the General Assembly passed an act to establish a governor's cabinet composed of administrative secretaries, and the Dept. of Treasury was placed under the Secretary of Finance control. From 1973 until 1984 the Dept. of Treasury was placed under the Secretary of Administration and Finance. In 1984 it was placed under the Secretary of Finance.
Scope and Content
State Treasurer's correspondence, 1962-1999, includes correspondence and subject files related to the Virginia Dept. of the Treasury. Contains correspondence, budget files, conference and association materials, legislation, memoranda, procedures, program files, reports, and general files of the Treasurer of Virginia. Also contains meeting materials and minutes of the Treasury Board, Virginia Higher Education Tuition Trust Fund, Virginia Housing Development Authority, Virginia Outdoors Foundation, Virginia Public School Authority, Virginia College Building Authority, and the Virginia Port Authority.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in original order.
Contents List
- State Treasurer's correspondence, 1962-1999.
  - Administrative Process Act, 1994 July. (Box 1)
  - Executive meeting procedures, undated. (Box 1)
  - Exective memorandums, 1997. (Box 1)
  - Executive Orders - Governor Allen, 1994-1997. (Box 1)
  - Governor's appointments, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Budget Symposium, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Office, 1993-1994. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Forum on Customer Service, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Office - General correspondence, 1998-1999. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Office - Gov. Gilmore, 1998. (Box 1)
  - Administration - Chief of Staff, 1998. (Box 1)
  - Car Tax, 1998-1999. (Box 1)
  - Administration "No Car Tax", 1998. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Office, 1997. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Office, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Office, 1995. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Office, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Office, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Governor's speech file, 1994-1999. (Box 1)
  - Transition to Governor Gilmore, 1997-1998. (Box 1)
  - Letters to Anthony Sgro - Governor's Office, 1996. (Box 1)
  - Governor Gilmore - Press releases and media, 1998. (Box 1)
  - Govenor's Office - Press releases and media, 1994-1997. (Box 1)
  - Govenor's Office - Governor's Commission on Electronic Communications, 1999. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Blue Ribbon Strike Force, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Blue Ribbon Strike Force recommendations, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Ceating a High Performance Work Force, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Higher Education Decentralization Symposium, 1997. (Box 1)
  - Higher Education Decentralization Report, 1992-1998. (Box 1)
  - Gov. Allen - State of the Commonwealth Debt report, 1997. (Box 1)
  - Tax Reform Task Force, 1998. (Box 1)
  - U.S. Small Business Administration, 1994-1995. (Box 1)
  - U.S. Treasury, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Administration - Other federal agencies, 1998. (Box 2)
  - Administration - State Quarter, 1998-1999. (Box 2)
  - Legislation, 1998. (Box 2)
  - Legislation, 1997. (Box 2)
  - Legislative Veto Sessions, 1997. (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Commonwealths Bond Debt, 1996. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly Session, 1997. (Box 2)
  - Legislation, 1996. (Box 2)
  - Legislation, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Legislation, 1994. (Box 2)
  - Budget, 1994. (Box 2)
  - Legislative Session, 1993. (Box 2)
  - GFOA Award for Excellenc (UCP System), 1999. (Box 2)
  - Senate Quality and Productivity Award, 1998-1999. (Box 2)
  - Kennedy School (Harvard) Innovations in American Government, 1998-1999. (Box 2)
  - Council of State Governments, 1990-1999. (Box 2)
  - Government Finance Officers Association (GFOA), 1995-1999. (Box 2)
  - MIRAC, 1996. (Box 2)
  - Government Finance Officers Association (GFOA), 1995-1999. (Box 2)
  - National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers and Treasurers (NASACT), 1992-1999. (Box 2)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST), 1994-1996. (Box 2)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST), 1997. (Box 2)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST), 1998. (Box 2)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST), 1993. (Box 3)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST), 1994. (Box 3)
  - Committee Assignments, 1994-1998. (Box 3)
  - College Savings Plan Network, 1995-1999. (Box 3)
  - Debt Management Network, 1995-1999. (Box 3)
  - Treasurer's Association of Virginia, 1994-1996. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Executive Institute Alumni Association (VEIAA), 1989-1999. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Executive Instititute Fall Conference, 1993. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Government Finance Officers Association (VGFOA), 1989-1995. (Box 3)
  - Task Force on Local Government Investment Pools, 1995. (Box 3)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST) - Task Force on Local Government Investment Pools, 1995. (Box 3)
  - State Treasurers Regional Association for Technical Assistance, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
  - Expenditure reports, 1996-1999. (Box 3)
  - Monthly Cash and Investment Report, 1991-1999. (Box 3)
  - Monthly Revenue Report, 1994-1999. (Box 3)
  - Monthly Statistical Report, 1994-1999. (Box 3)
  - Quarterly Management Report, 1996-1998. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Reports, 1994-1999. (Box 4)
  - Weekly report to the Secretary of Finance, 1998-1999. (Box 4)
  - Treasurer's correspondence, 1994-1999. (Box 4)
  - General correspondence, 1995-1998. (Box 4)
  - General correspondence, 1995-1996. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence file, 1995. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence file, 1996. (Box 4)
  - Brotherhood of Teamsters - Merrill Lynch, 1994. (Box 4)
  - General Management - Senate Productivity and Quality Award, 1998-1999. (Box 4)
  - Treasurer's Memoranda - Agency-wide, 1995-1998. (Box 4)
  - Treasurer's Memoranda - Official, 1998. (Box 4)
  - Treasurer's Memoranda - Directors, 1994-1996. (Box 4)
  - James Monroe Building Committee, 1989-1992. (Box 4)
  - Office of the Attorney General - Notice of Service Transmittals, 1989-1994. (Box 4)
  - General correspondence, 1996-1999. (Box 4)
  - Agency regulations, 1993-1998. (Box 4)
  - Budget, 1996-1998. (Box 4)
  - Budget benchmark, 1996-1998. (Box 4)
  - Goal setting and performance, 1996-1998. (Box 4)
  - Budget/Planning Retreat, 1995. (Box 4)
  - Budget/Planning Retreat, 1994-1995. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget instructions, 1997. (Box 5)
  - Meetings with the Secretary of Finance and Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1997. (Box 5)
  - Budget submissions, 1997. (Box 5)
  - Other Dept. of Planning and Budget submissions, 1997. (Box 5)
  - Financial Policy - Dept. of General Services Procurement Review, 1996. (Box 5)
  - Summary of accomplishments, 1996. (Box 5)
  - Goals and objectives, 1996. (Box 5)
  - Goals and objectives, 1996-1998. (Box 5)
  - Goals and objectives FY1995 - Summary of accomplishments, 1994. (Box 5)
  - Accomplishments, 1994. (Box 5)
  - Financial statements, 1995-1998. (Box 5)
  - Management Reports - Dept. of the Treasury, 1998. (Box 5)
  - Freedom of Information Act, undated. (Box 5)
  - Policy and procedures, 1995. (Box 5)
  - Financial policy - Performance measures, 1996-1998. (Box 5)
  - Procurement workplan, 1993-1998. (Box 5)
  - Purchasing, 1994-1999. (Box 5)
  - Records management, 1992-1995. (Box 5)
  - Records retention, 1992-1996. (Box 5)
  - Financial Policy - Reprographic Study, 1996. (Box 5)
  - Treasury Newsletters, 1994-1995. (Box 5)
  - Internal audit - General, 1994-1999. (Box 5)
  - FY 99 Audit Reports, 1998-1999. (Box 5)
  - FY 98 Audit Reports, 1997-1998. (Box 5)
  - FY 97 Audit Reports, 1996-1997. (Box 5)
  - FY 98 Monthly Status Reports, 1997-1998. (Box 5)
  - FY 97 Monthly Status Reports, 1996-1997. (Box 5)
  - FY 96 Monthly Status Reports, 1995-1996. (Box 5)
  - FY 99 Quarterly Status Reports, 1998-1999. (Box 5)
  - FY 98 Quarterly Status Reports, 1997-1998. (Box 5)
  - FY 96 Quarterly Status Reports, 1995-1996. (Box 5)
  - Quality Assurance Review, 1997-1999. (Box 5)
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1991-1993. (Box 5)
  - General correspondence, 1991-1998. (Box 6)
  - General correspondence, 195-1996. (Box 6)
  - General correspondence, 1992-1993. (Box 6)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1991-1997. (Box 6)
  - Agency Leadership Workshop, 1996-1997. (Box 6)
  - Staff Development Retreat, 1995 June 3. (Box 6)
  - Staff Development Retreat, 1996 June 3. (Box 6)
  - Agency Leadership Workshop, 1995 June 2. (Box 6)
  - Treasury Management Retreat, 1997. (Box 6)
  - Customer Service Plan, 1994. (Box 6)
  - Treasury Management Retreat, 1994 Nov 3-4. (Box 6)
  - Goals and Objectives FY 1995 - Summary of accomplishments, 1994. (Box 6)
  - Treasury Staff Retreat, 1996-1997. (Box 6)
  - Personnel - Telecommuting, 1996. (Box 6)
  - Personnel - Treasurer's Award, 1996. (Box 6)
  - General correspondence, 1996. (Box 6)
  - General correspondence, 1996-1999. (Box 6)
  - General correspondence, 1995-1999. (Box 6)
  - College Savings Bonds Program, 1990. (Box 6)
  - College Savings Bonds Program, 1989-1993. (Box 6)
  - Management companies, 1994. (Box 6)
  - Asset managers, 1994-199. (Box 6)
  - Virginia Railway Express, 1999 Feb 17. (Box 6)
  - Investment Program, 1994-1997. (Box 6)
  - Investment Compliance Reports, 1995. (Box 6)
  - Interest Forecast, 1996-1998. (Box 6)
  - External Fixed Managers, 1996-1999. (Box 6)
  - Crestar/Rt. 28 investments, 1994. (Box 6)
  - Electronic benefit transfer, 1997. (Box 6)
  - College Savings Plan, 1992-1993. (Box 6)
  - College Savings Plan, 1989-1993. (Box 6)
  - Public Finance, 1997. (Box 7)
  - State Treasurer of Virginia, 1996. (Box 7)
  - Legg Mason, 1996. (Box 7)
  - Standard and Poor's Managed Fund Ratings, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Mercer Investment Reports, 1997-1998. (Box 7)
  - Investment performance evaluation, 1999. (Box 7)
  - Total Return Pool Compliance Report, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Investment performance evaluation, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Total Return Pool Compliance Report, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Total Return Pool Compliance Report, 1998 July-Sept. (Box 7)
  - Total Return Pool Compliance Report, 1998 Apr-June. (Box 7)
  - Total Return Pool Compliance Report, 1998 July. (Box 7)
  - Total Return Pool Compliance Report, 1998 Jan-Mar. (Box 7)
  - Investment performance evaluation, 1998 Mar. (Box 7)
  - Western Asset, 1998 Apr. (Box 7)
  - Fidelity Management Trust Company investment management, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Wellington Management Company - Portfolio Review, 1998 Apr. (Box 7)
  - Sovran Capital Management presentation, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Merganser Capital Management Corporation, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Local Government Investment Pool Guidelines, 1995-1997. (Box 7)
  - Local Government Investment Pool, 1995-1999. (Box 7)
  - Virginia Local Government Investment Pool, Inc., 1987-1992. (Box 7)
  - Cash management - Virginia Education Loan Authority, transfer to Treasury Bond, 19. (Box 7)
  - Merchant Credit Card Program, 1990. (Box 7)
  - First Chicago, 1993. (Box 7)
  - U.S. Treasury, 1993. (Box 7)
  - s.240 Private Securities, 1995. (Box 7)
  - Save for America campaign, 1995. (Box 7)
  - Savings Bond Program, 1987-1996. (Box 7)
  - South African Divestiture, 1991-1993. (Box 7)
  - Bear Stearns - Information prepared for the Dept. of the Treasury, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Norwest Corporate Trust Services, 1997. (Box 7)
  - Sovran Capital Management presentation, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Scott and Stringfellow, Inc. - Public finance, 1997. (Box 7)
  - Unisys, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Artemis Capital Group, 1998. (Box 7)
  - JHM Capital Management, 1998. (Box 7)
  - Golman, Sachs and Company, 1995. (Box 7)
  - Virginia Retirement System, 1996. (Box 7)
  - Wellington Management, 1996. (Box 7)
  - Western Asset Management, 1996-1999. (Box 7)
  - General correspondence, 1996-1999. (Box 7)
  - Debt management, 1995. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - Media, 1999. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - Advisory Committee, 1996. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - Airport financing, 1998. (Box 8)
  - Bond issues / disclosures, 1994-1998. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - NRO, 1998. (Box 8)
  - 9(b) Bonds / General obligation, 1993-1997. (Box 8)
  - General obligation bonds, 1994-1998. (Box 8)
  - 9(c) Bonds / Higher education - VSU, 1995-1998. (Box 8)
  - 9(d) Bonds, 1996. (Box 8)
  - Proposals, 1996. (Box 8)
  - Higher education, 1998. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - Transportation, 1996-1998. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - VCBA, 1996-1999. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - VPBA, 1998. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - VPSA, 1996-1998. (Box 8)
  - Transportation Trust Fund, 1996-1998. (Box 8)
  - Bond Buyer, 1995-1999. (Box 8)
  - Bond Buyer, 1996-1998. (Box 8)
  - Bond Buyer's Watch, 1996-1998. (Box 8)
  - Big Stone Gap Prison Project, 1995. (Box 8)
  - Commonwealth Debt, 1995-1997. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - Federal laws and regulations, 1997. (Box 8)
  - Innovation Technologyy Authority Refunding (CIT), 1996. (Box 8)
  - Industrial Development Bonds, 1996-1999. (Box 8)
  - Institute of Human Virology, 1995. (Box 8)
  - Debt management - Internet, 1998. (Box 8)
  - Juvenile Correctional Centers, 1997. (Box 8)
  - MCV - UVA restructuring, 1995-1998. (Box 8)
  - Master Equipment Leasin Program, 1990-1998. (Box 8)
  - Municipal Security Rulemaking Board (MSRB), 1990-1997. (Box 8)
  - Northern Virginia Transportation Revenue Bonds, 1990-1993. (Box 8)
  - Public Resources Advisory Group, 1993-1999. (Box 8)
  - Public Securities Association, 1989-1995. (Box 9)
  - Fitch, 1990-1998. (Box 9)
  - Moody's Investment Services, 1989-1998. (Box 9)
  - Standard and Poor's, 1994-1998. (Box 9)
  - Standard and Poor's, 1995. (Box 9)
  - Rating Agency presentation, 1999. (Box 9)
  - Rating Agency presentation, 1998. (Box 9)
  - VCBA - Lehman Brothers, 1997. (Box 9)
  - Rating Agency presentation, 1997. (Box 9)
  - Rating Agencies, 1993. (Box 9)
  - Rating Agencie, 1996. (Box 9)
  - Rating Agencies, 1992. (Box 9)
  - Financial World, 1995. (Box 9)
  - Treasury Board Regional Jail Financing Program, 1994-1998. (Box 9)
  - Short term borrowing, 1990. (Box 9)
  - State aid intercept, 1989-1991. (Box 9)
  - Tax-Exempt Commercial Paper, 1995-1998. (Box 9)
  - Tidewater Community College Project, 1993. (Box 9)
  - Transportation Trust Fund, 1994-1997. (Box 9)
  - UVA Neurological Institute Project, 1995. (Box 9)
  - Introduction to BT Alex Brown, Inc., 1998. (Box 9)
  - Introduction to J.P. Morgan and Market Opportunities, 1997. (Box 9)
  - Froley, Revy Investment Company, Inc., 1997. (Box 9)
  - Citibank, 1997. (Box 10)
  - Hopkins and Sutter, 1997. (Box 10)
  - Fairmount Capital Advisors, Inc., 1997. (Box 10)
  - SBC Warburg, 1997. (Box 10)
  - Morgan Stanley, 1997. (Box 10)
  - Paine Webber, 1995-1998. (Box 10)
  - VCU Biotech Center, 1994-1998. (Box 10)
  - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 1996-1998. (Box 10)
  - Virginia Horse Center, 1992. (Box 10)
  - General correspondence, 1996-1999. (Box 10)
  - Evaluation of Treasury's bank reconciliation function, 1997. (Box 10)
  - Bank reconciliation, 1996-1997. (Box 10)
  - Operations - Disaster recovery, undated. (Box 10)
  - Central Mail Service, 1993-1998. (Box 10)
  - Literary Fund, 1989-1998. (Box 10)
  - Operations - Risk Assessment, 1994-1996. (Box 10)
  - Public Financial Management (PFM), 1992-1994. (Box 10)
  - Securities for Public Deposits, 1996-1999. (Box 10)
  - State Non-Arbitrage Program (SNAP), 1999. (Box 10)
  - State Non-Arbitrage Program (SNAP), 1998. (Box 10)
  - State Non-Arbitrage Program (SNAP), 1997. (Box 10)
  - State Non-Arbitrage Program (SNAP), 1996. (Box 10)
  - Zip plus 4 Program, 1987-1988. (Box 10)
  - Unclaimed Property - General correspondence, 1999. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property - General correspondence, 1998. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property - General correspondence, 1997. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property - General correspondence, 1996. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property audits, 1997-1999. (Box 11)
  - Audit, 1995-1999. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property audits, 1997. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property - Claims, 1995-1997. (Box 11)
  - Davenport and Company, 1994-1997. (Box 11)
  - Delaware v. New York, 1995. (Box 11)
  - Escheats law, 1995-1997. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property - NAPPCO, 1996-1999. (Box 11)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Insurance and Banking, 1997 Dec. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property - NAUPA, 1996-1998. (Box 11)
  - NAUPA - Annapolis, MD, 1998 Apr. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property - NAUPA, UCP National Database, 1995-1997. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property - Security and Exchange Commission regulations, 1997. (Box 11)
  - Unclaimed Property - State Street, 1998. (Box 12)
  - Statesman's Park Landfill, 1993-1994. (Box 12)
  - Statesman's Park Landfill, 1991-1993. (Box 12)
  - Statesman's Park Landfill, 1990. (Box 12)
  - Unclaimed Property - Swiss Dormant Accounts (Holocaust Survivors), 1997-1998. (Box 12)
  - Unclaimed Property - Systems, 1998-1999. (Box 12)
  - Unclaimed Property - Sale of UCP System, 1997-1998. (Box 12)
  - Tanglible Property internal controls, 1996. (Box 12)
  - Trigon - Blue Cross, 1995-1997. (Box 12)
  - Uniform law, 1995-1997. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1999 Dec. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1999 Sep-Nov. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1996-1999. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1996-1999. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Correspondence, 1994-1999. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Board of Commissioners, 1999. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Gateway to America, 1999 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1999 Jan. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Gateway to America, 1999 Jan. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1998. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Gateway to America, 1998 Nov. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Board meeting, 1998 Nov. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority - General correspondence, 1998. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority - General correspondence, 1997-1998. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1998 Sept. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1998 June. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Executive Committee meeting, 1998 May. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1998 Jan. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Correspondence, 1997. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Port Facilities Revenue Bonds, 1997. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1997 May. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Capital Outlay Manual, 1997 May. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1997 Apr. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1997 Mar. (Box 13)
  - Finance / Planning Committee, 1997 Nov. (Box 13)
  - Historic Preservation Foundation, 1995. (Box 13)
  - VSBFA Loan Committee, 1999. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Higher Education Tuition Trust Fund, 1998-1999. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund, 1999. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund, 1998. (Box 13)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund Board meeting, 1998 July. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund Board meeting, 1998 May. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund Board meeting, 1998 Nov. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund Board meeting, 1998 Mar. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund Board meeting, 1998 Jan. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund, 1996. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund, 1994-1995. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Higher Education Trust Fund, 1994. (Box 14)
  - Virginia State Parks Foundation, 1998. (Box 14)
  - Virginia State Parks Foundation, 1996 May. (Box 14)
  - Virginia State Parks Foundation, 1995 Apr. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation - Correspondence, 1998-1999. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation - Board of Trustees meeting, 1999 Dec. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation - Board of Trustees meeting, 1999 Oct. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation - Board of Trustees meeting, 1999 June. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation - Board of Trustees meeting, 1999 Apr. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation - Board of Trustees meeting, 1998 Dec. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation - Board of Trustees meeting, 1998 Oct. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation - Board of Trustees meeting, 1998 Dec. (Box 15)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation - Board of Trustees meeting, 1998 Apr. (Box 15)
  - Susan F. Dewey - Travel, 1999. (Box 15)
  - Southern State Treasurers Conference, 1999. (Box 15)
  - NAST - Southern State Treasurers Conference, 1999. (Box 15)
  - NAST - Legislative Conference, 1999. (Box 15)
  - Northern Virginia Electric Coop - Security Exchange Commission, 1999. (Box 15)
  - Susan F. Dewey - Travel, 1998. (Box 15)